Nathan Rogers

(719)-229-0865 • nathan.rogers.d@gmail.com • github.com/nathan-rogers

SUMMARY

As an Army veteran, I have spent years cultivating an insatiable desire to learn. Starting with Satellite Communication technologies, painting in Photoshop, using digital audio emulation with the AxeFx and Line 6 products, and most recently learning to code, I have placed myself in situations where I am forced to adjust and acquire new skills. My dream since leaving the military has been to find an open and dynamic team environment where individuals are encouraged to learn and adapt. I welcome the opportunity to grow as a member of your team while working toward my goal of becoming a senior-level, full-stack developer in Java or .NET within the next five years.

SKIIIS

· HTML5 · C# · Java · LINQ

· JavaScript · VisualStudio · Eclipse · PhotoShop

· AngularJS · SQL · jQuery · Scrum Master

EDUCATION

SeedPaths – Denver, CO Apr. 2015 – June 2015

8-week software development boot camp focusing on the fundamentals of .NET programming.

Self Study in Java - Colorado Springs, CO

Jan. 2015 - Mar. 2015

• Studied Java under a 20-year professional and instructor at Phoenix University, preparing me for my impending attendance at SeedPaths.

University of Northern Colorado - Greeley, CO

Aug. 2014 - Dec. 2014

· Accepted into the Classical Guitar program based on a practice schedule of 5-10 hours a day, 5 days a week for 2 years to prepare for the audition, and accrued over 2,000 hours in total.

Southwest Texas Junior College - Del Rio, TX

Jan. 2006 - May 2006

- · Studied Personal Computer Hardware.
- · Studied Network Administration using Windows 2003 Server Edition.

EXPERIENCE

Stag Tobacconist - Colorado Springs, CO

Mar. 2013 - Mar. 2015

Assisted in maintaining an inventory worth of over \$1 million in cigars and cigar accounterments, requiring a keen attention to detail
and effective communication.

US ARMY Satellite Communication Operator - Camp Leatherneck, Afghanistan

July 2007 - July 2013

- Deployed to Afghanistan in support of 2nd Marine Expeditionary Force 2011 as a part of a 6-person Army Space Support Team that used HTML, KML, GoogleEarth and MS Office Suite to develop products that fused data for tactical use by various forward deployed units.
- Developed PowerPoint products which were used by the office of the CENTCOM Commander, General David Patreus, to provide time-sensitive information for use in strategic decision making.
- Cross-trained team members, civilians and Marines in Satellite Communication operation.
- Earned Army Commendation Medal (ARCOM) for service during deployment.

REFERENCES

· Available on request